<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dale Hassinger on </title>
    <link>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/tags/dale-hassinger/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dale Hassinger on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/tags/dale-hassinger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About this site</title>
      <link>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/</guid>
      <description>Your Resource to learn about Automation, Monitoring, Logging, more&amp;hellip; Monitoring:
Automation:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About this site</title>
      <link>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/about/</guid>
      <description>Title: Unlocking the Potential
Topics: VMware Aria Suite and more&amp;hellip;
Introduction:
Welcome to our Blog site! We&amp;rsquo;re excited to have you here as part of the vCommunity. This platform was born out of a passion for sharing knowledge and expertise regarding the VMware Aria Suite of Products. We recognize that our customers often have burning questions and inquiries about these powerful solutions. Our mission is to provide clear and insightful answers to these queries, benefiting not only the inquisitive individuals who ask but also the broader community who might have similar concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action Constants and Secrets</title>
      <link>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/aria-automation/assembler/action-constant-and-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/aria-automation/assembler/action-constant-and-secrets/</guid>
      <description>VMware Aria Automation | Action Constants and Secrets: VMware Aria Automation 8.14 was used for this Blog Post. When new versions of VMware Aria Automation are released, the code may need to be changed.
All the source code for this Blog is saved in my GitHub Repository. Click on the links within the blog to access the code.
I wanted to share how I use Action Constants and Secrets within VMware Aria Automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Form Versioning</title>
      <link>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/aria-automation/service-broker/custom-form-versioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/aria-automation/service-broker/custom-form-versioning/</guid>
      <description>Custom Form Versioning Demo: VMware Aria Automation 8.12 Released: With the release of VMware Aria Automation 8.12, Custom Form Versioning was added to the Product. I use a lot Custom Forms with the Automation that I create, so I wanted to make sure I understood how the versioning feature worked. If you never did versioning before, this Blog Post should save you some time getting started and help you understand how the new features was designed to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerCLI</title>
      <link>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/powercli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/powercli/</guid>
      <description>PowerCLI Scripts:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Links</title>
      <link>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/resource-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dalehassinger.github.io/vcommunity/resource-links/</guid>
      <description>Links to some of my favorite Bloggers and Content:
vCROCS | GitHub Repository: vCROCS | GitHub Repository Salt | Formulas Repository Bloggers | Youtube: Brock Peterson - VMware Aria Operations Master Christopher Kusek - The Forgotten Manual Tech Cosmin Trif - VMware Aria Suite Master LucD - PowerShell Master William Lam - VMware Master Yellow Bricks Don Horrox Corey Blaz VMware: VMware Operations Management Book - Great Book! code.VMware.com - Samples/Resources Learn vRealize Automation Learn SaltStack Config blogs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
